Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun has as its leader a man named Licht, a mage with a coveted four-leaf clover grimoire.
Six years ago, he formed a terror group bent on opposing the Clover Kingdom.
It now counts some fifty mages as its members.
Beneath Licht are the three ranking members known as the Third Eye, Raya, Veto, and Fana.
Their power far outstrips the others.
The organization's members harbor a deep hatred of the Clover Kingdom, which drives their acts of terrorism against our country.
Their ultimate goal is to establish a sovereign state.
That all sound correct so far?
Yes.
Now then, the juiciest tit-fit is probably this.
The traitor who cooperated with the Eye of the Midnight Sun is one of you, our Magic Knight Captains.
Huh? One of us? No, that can't be true!
I knew it.
But which captain?
You're the reason Captain Foigolion got hurt.
But why? Why would one of the captains turn traitor?
It's not all over the last day….
It is.
What victims do they have to earliest decide the final fight?
You can't issue the most underground, or you can find the時間 at returning to the都.
You can't honor them to fight them either.
I don't either draw your hand.
Don't, yes.
The kitty's contain metadata, or thepak andETe.
And that's where the perfect video is,
from yourquest,
and keep in mind,
and eat the range!
And we challenge ourselves
to beat ourselves
so we can't lose ourselves
and make ourselves
way,
because we're normally
trying to stay
me
Let go of the flesh.
All right. Now, will you tell us?
Who among those gathered here is the traitorous captain who collaborated with the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Go on. Tell us their name.
The traitor.
Is the Purple Orca's captain.
Gelder Poizot.
Ugh. Ridiculous. What are you trying to say?
These two are terrorists guilty of attacking the royal capital itself.
You would have to be crazy to believe a word out of their mouths.
I've never given anyone cause to doubt my loyalty to this kingdom.
Well, that isn't exactly true.
I have heard a few distasteful rumors regarding you.
Is that all, Charlotte? I've heard a great deal more than a few.
No way. Are you guys serious?
Sure are. There are rumors all over the damn place. It's crazy.
And now it seems they weren't baseless after all.
I always knew that you were up to something sneaky, but I never imagined even you would stoop to this level.
This isn't funny. There's obviously been a mistake.
Yes. Those two are trying to set me up and you're all falling for it.
Impossible. They've answered honestly with all the information at their disposal.
Anything said under the spell's compulsion is true, without a doubt.
There you have it, Hammy.
Who are you calling Hammy?
Hey now, calm down.
Why don't you get Mushroomhead to use his fancy spell on you?
He can sneak a little peek inside that head of yours.
If you've been a good ham, you'll have nothing to worry about.
Apart from the stupid nickname, I agree completely.
If you're truly innocent, you should jump at the chance to prove it.
Well, I... don't know.
Hey, what's the matter there, Hammy?
You get shy all of a sudden?
Most disgraceful, Gelder.
Such a betrayal is unforgivable.
It should be a capital offense.
So you really are a traitor then?
You jerk!
You betrayed your fellow captain!
No!
This is some kind of trap!
I'll find a way to clear my name.
But for now, I'll have to retreat!
Transparacy creation magic!
Activating the invisible mage!
He's gone!
Ha! He's making a run for it.
Things are getting serious now.
Not good.
He's invisible.
And as long as he is, all magic will pass right through him.
So basically, we're screwed.
None of our attack spells will work on the faster while he's like this.
What?!
So he's invincible now?!
Transparacy creation magic!
Invisible troops!
That ought to keep them occupied for a bit.
I can't let him head away.
Hey!
Come on, Dorothy!
This isn't the time to be sleeping on the job!
I don't suppose anyone knows how to chase somebody you can't see!
Yami?
Don't worry.
We got this.
Did they think I would just stand there and let them capture me?
With my magic, I'm untouchable!
This is the power that made me a magic knight captain in the first place!
Then there's my incomparable business acumen, which made me an influential tycoon!
Between the two, I've become a great mage rich in both money and might!
My story isn't going to end here.
Thanks to my magical talent and financial genius, I'm unstoppable!
Oh!
Gotcha!
What?
Where did you come from?
That's impossible!
You saw me through my magic?
Little brat!
How did you attack me?
Well, ol' Hammy's transparency magic may be able to hide him
But hiding his key is another story
And since an anti-magic sword isn't, you know, magic
It can hit him just fine
Well, I guess we know what his natural enemy is now
A magicless boy who knows how to read key
You can't win! I'm a magic knight captain!
You are some magicless commoner!
Yes, that's excellent
The writhing on the floor like a desperate fish look suits you quite well
No way!
You're a magic knight captain! You're supposed to be better than this!
Now come back and face me!
All right then
If you want to die that badly, I'll help you
But don't say I didn't give you a fair warning
Well, hello there
If you could just stay still a moment, please
Picture magic, spring of restriction
Wow, Mr. Poizat, you make a wonderful painting
And I know just what to call it, too
Yes, the drowning captain
What'd you think?
No way! What kind of magic is that?
Honestly, Ryl, you and your half-baked nonsense
Yeah, well, somebody had to do something
Or else you'd destroy this entire building
His magic makes all spells pass through him, but not physical objects
Therefore, we need only attack with non-magical items
If this building must fall to bring him down, commoners can easily rebuild it
I missed the chance to fight a fellow captain in real combat
It would've been fun, too, slicing up that ham into tiny little pieces
Magic knight captains can't stand around twiddling their thumbs while there's a traitor waiting to be caught
At least gotta strike a pose or something
Seriously, are you still snoozing?
Although you did manage to keep up with us, so I guess you're pretty sharp for being asleep
What a pitiful excuse for a man
Running like a coward
He was a failure as a captain long before this
Why is Yami paying so much attention to Dorothy?
Is she the type of woman he likes?
Enough
Let's leave it there for now
Consider this
Someone else may be controlling him with magic
Well, I'm glad the rest of you were here to help wrangle our traitor
I'm afraid I couldn't have gone so easy on him
These people are crazy!
And they're the best of the magic knights
The best mages in the entire kingdom?
Hey, I don't know what you just did, but it was amazing
How'd you know where Captain Poizot was?
And how'd you break his transparency spell?
Um, well, I just...
Never mind, I'm real and I'm 19, who are you?
I'm Asta and I'm 15
I can't believe you're only 19 years old and you're a captain
Ah, so you're younger than me then
I think we should be friends, what do you say?
Friends? With a captain?
Seriously?
Okay, great!
Yay! Awesome!
You know, these guys, they're older and
I mean, talking to them, it's tough, so
Right?
Yeah!
Boring!
Man!
We know we can hear you right
And who the hell are you?
Call anyone boring
All right
So far, all you've done is make excuses
Let's hear the truth
Now, Gelder
Have the answers you've given us up to this point all been truthful?
They have
You know, I have to hand it to you, Hammy
That's quite an impressive list
Let's see here
Beating up your own squad members
Misappropriating magic tools
And smuggling dangerous magic drugs
You were way dirty before the whole traitor thing
Now, with all that dirt, you're more of a black bull than anyone in my squad
Well, in your case, I guess blackened ham would be more accurate
Can't
Do you ever stop running your mouth, Yami?
No wonder he didn't want us reading his mind with Marx's spell
You didn't mention his worst crime
Abducting a guardian mage
That's direct cooperation with the Eye of the Midnight Sun
At least now we know how they were able to invade the royal capital
The fool was so blinded by the offer of rare magic tools
He made a deal with terrorists
So he's greedy and immoral
Does that really surprise anybody?
The Eye of the Midnight Sun likely killed the abducted guardian mage
Shortly after the attack on the capital
His actions are both unprecedented and unforgivable
He was a magic knight
Charged with protecting our people
Yet he sold them out instead
If word of this got out, the populace might panic
So we won't be making this matter public
I want you to take a good look at your squads
Make sure none of them have ties to the enemy
This cannot happen again
Yes, sir
Well
I put on quite the performance
Nobody can see through my copy transformation magic
So
Which person in the room was actually me?
That ought to keep them from being suspicious for a while at least
I'm sorry for keeping you two
I won't detain you for long
It's a terrible feeling
To be betrayed by somebody who once fought alongside you
I sprinted at full speed to get where I am
But as a result I may have made mistakes along the way
Did you keep us behind to tell us that?
Because if so, Julius, I gotta say you picked the wrong guys
There was one more piece of information the Midnight Sun members revealed during their questioning
Asta?
Remember the hideout they took you to after you were captured?
And the mysterious stone tablet that was hidden there?
That thing?
According to our captives
They call the gems embedded in that tablet magic stones
They believe that gathering them will allow them to be reborn into their true forms
With close ties to the mana
Thereby granting them immense power
Apparently that was the reason they targeted Fuegolion
Because of the magic stone he wore
They think they're gonna be reborn?
You sure they haven't been reading too many of those fantasy novels?
We can't know for sure whether it's true
But their belief is very real
And that's enough to convince me that we must keep them from getting the stones at all costs
Uh-huh, uh-huh, and?
Four stones remain to be gathered
And from what our captives said
It seems they know the location of one of them
Hmm, where's that?
The Underwater Temple
One of the strong magic regions
That makes sense
Oh yeah, of course
Water those again?
If you're not actually gonna use this thing
I'll go ahead and crush it for you
Strong magic regions
As the name suggests
They're areas of great magic power
Various magic phenomena in these places make them difficult to access
One such region
An especially hazardous one
Is known as the Underwater Temple
You can think of the dungeon you and your colleagues conquered before as the beginner's version of this place
You mean
It's even more dangerous?
So, we have to get there before this Eye of the Midnight Sun does and make off with this magic stone thingy
Is that the general idea?
That's right
And I believe the best people for this mission will be found in the Black Bulls
Who are unique among the Magic Knights
Because of the number of its members unfettered by family or social standing
We can't forget
There may still be traitors among the Magic Knights
So, will you do it?
You're the Wizard King, aren't you?
If you want something done, just tell us to do it
And you're right
If you're worried about connections
I don't exactly have a whole lot holding me back
Look at that freak
He's not from here, you know
He washed her from some other country
Lives alone on the coast
He's dangerous
Just look at those eyes
I wish he'd just go back where he belongs
No way!
Some grubby foreigner get a grimoire?
Probably full of useless spells
Bet we can use our magic to get rid of him
What kind of magic is that?
The scary kind
That's just freaky
Yeah
I got a grimoire just like them
But that didn't make me any less of a foreigner in their eyes
In exchange for nothing holding me down
I'd be alone all my life
Or so I thought
Wow!
Was that dark magic?
What the?
Awesome!
I've never seen it before
Please, you've got to let me get a closer look
Yeah, no
Who are you, mister?
I, uh, well
I'm no one to be suspicious of
I assure you
I'm just a magic knight captain
Out walking in disguise
What's a magic knight, captain?
Huh?
You don't know?
Okay
Why don't you come with me and I'll show you?
I think you have real potential
I'll pass
Come on, it'll be fun
I'll treat you to dinner
I'm in
Okay, can't blame a guy for...
Wait, you'll come?
Uh, yeah
If you're buying dinner, I'll definitely come
You know, you're a really funny guy
And that was that
I've been stuck with you ever since
I'll use all the power I've got to prove that you're not wrong about this
To show you that you haven't made any mistakes
Yami saluting
Thank you, Yami
I'm counting on you
Oh, and Asta
Yes, sir!
I'm starting to think it may have been fate you're joining Yami's squad
You see, strong magic regions have powerful mana force fields that prevent outsiders from entering
I doubt anyone would be able to get in without your anti-magic
And your experience battling with the eye of the midnight sun will serve you well, I'm sure
I'm counting on you, too
Yes, sir!
I've never seen someone injure themselves giving a salute
He's a funny one
I can see why you picked him for your crew
You're as stiff as a board in there
Guess even the comic relief gets nervous sometimes
I'm more than just a comic relief
Well, the thing is, I've never really had somebody I look up to
Like the Wizard King actually expect anything from me like this before
He can't use magic and he thinks he'll get into a night squad?
Right, like that's gonna happen
Actually, I don't think anybody's expected anything from me before
Huh
I let you into my squad because I thought you could hack it
So keep working hard, kid
Yes, sir!
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
We're going to the beach!
That's a real man's destination right there!
Nothing's manlier than the beach!
Am I right?
Yeah, this is awesome!
I've never even seen the ocean before!
Me neither, little Rasta!
Beach!
There's nothing better than relaxing in the sun on a hot day with a nice cold drink
Hello, ladies!
Can I offer anyone an original handcrafted cocktail?
You look divine in those swimsuits, by the way!
Swimsuits?
If we're going to go to the beach, does that mean I have to wear one?
I don't know if I can handle something like that!
Maybe I should just stay here?
There's so many kinds of seafood, just waiting to be grilled up by the shore!
The culinary possibilities are endless!
Now, now, ladies, they're bloody to go around!
Pshuuu!
Captain?
Huh?
What kind of souvenir do you think I should get Marie?
Hey, sharks are supposed to be super strong, right?
I hope the sharks eat you both!
A swimsuit?
Seriously?
I just can't!
I can lend you one if you need it!
Aaaaaaaah!
Beach!
Shut it!
We're going to the beach to work, not to play, you got it?
Yes, sir!
The underwater temple, huh?
I wonder if it's as cool as it sounds!
We'll be right back.
Come on!
The captain was crazy tough when he was young!
Hey, that's from back around the time we met.
How nostalgic.
You're not mad for me then or now, kid.
Not yet.
I'm not done.
Go right, counterattack!
Yeah, gotcha!
Now left!
What are you?
How about we put the controllers down and have a real battle?
I don't want to game over!
What should I do?
If we're going to the beach, I'll need a swimsuit.
I have to buy a new one.
I wonder what kind Asta likes.
Black Clover, page 40.
A Black Beach story.
Wait, what am I saying?
I don't care what Dorksta thinks.